

SLIL PUANGPOOM

Software Engineer





Professional Summary

For official job I have 3 years experienced in full stack web development with ASP.NET Core technology. For my personal I am eager to learn new things in react web framework, API with node.js (express) and get some freelance job for real world project so I'm confident to work with them like my official skill too.



Work History

2019-10 -Current

Software Engineer

Hatari wireless, Bangkok

- Worked closely with UX/UI designer to analyst user requirements.
- Full stack web development
 - Front-end : ASP.NET Core MVC with javascript , jquery , css (boostrap), html
 - Back-end : RESTful API's ASP.NET Core with N-Tier architecture (data , business , presentation) .
- Deploy docker containers on AWS (ECR) and AWS lambda

2021-01 -2021-04

Freelance Full stack developer

- Backoffice web management for a factory.
- Front-end: React
- Back-end: Express web framework for Node.js API

2018-10 -2019-09

Programmer Analyst

Hatari wireless, Bangkok

- Design relational database with ER-diagram and develop with Microsoft SQL Server.
- Design and Develop RESTful API's with ASP.NET Core web framework technology (C# programming language).
- Database access with Entity Framework (object-relational mapping)
- Maintain and support for existing project.



Education

2013-05 -2017-07 **Bachelor of Engineering: Industrial Engineering**

Chulalongkorn University



Address

Bangkok, Bangsue, 10800

Phone

087 500 6783

E-mail

slil.puangpoom@gmail.com

Birthdate

12 / 07 / 1995 (25 years)



www.blinkmecode.com



C# (.NET Core)

React

Express (Node.js)

HTML

CSS (Bootstrap, Tailwind)

Javascript

Jquery

MSSQL

MySQL

Docker